Finding Aid for Eugene B. Power papers, 1937-1993
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Eugene B. Power papers
1937-1993
Power, Eugene B., 1905-
852048 Aa 2; UAm
Founder and director of University Microfilms, Ann Arbor, Michigan, and member of the board of regents of the University of Michigan. Correspondence, agendas of meetings, memoranda, reports and printed material relating to his business and University activities; and photographs.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
144 linear feet
19 microfilms
1 oversize volumes
1 oversize folders
The collection (Donor No. 4500 ) was the gift of Mr. Power and began coming to the library in 1967. Periodic additions ensued until his death in 1993.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Eugene Barnum Power was born in 1905 in Traverse City, Michigan. He received his BA in 1927 and his MBA in 1930, both from the University of Michigan. In 1929 he married the former Sadye L. Harwick and moved to Ann Arbor, Michigan, where his son, Philip H., was born in 1938.
Eugene Power was an entrepreneur with many and widely varied interests. He was a founder of the modern microfilm industry and a pioneer in the information revolution. A public servant, he was a regent of the University of Michigan and member of the council of the National Endowment for the Humanities. As a philanthropist, he founded the Power Foundation and established the Power Exchange Scholarships.
Eugene Power early in his career began investigating methods of reproducing and distributing research materials. He became convinced that the just-emerging technology of textual microphotography was the ideal medium for making widely available the treasures of the world's libraries. In 1938, he founded University Microfilms, Inc. and began a series of inventions and projects that would make microfilm research an everyday part of the scholar's life. He first arranged to have photographed all British books printed before 1640 with a microfilm camera that he invented. Positive copies of these films he then sold to research libraries. He next applied the technology of microfilm to the publication of doctoral dissertations. These dissertations then became available on film, Xerographic copy or larger offset printed editions. Other projects followed: the microfilming of newspaper and periodical files and the filming of manuscript and other unique materials.
Eugene Power was a proponent of the idea of "editions of one." He believed it was possible and profitable to produce in editions of any size any textual material in existence. Power realized that if a book or any other text in print could be photographed and stored in microfilm form, it could then be reproduced, on demand, in editions as low as one.
In 1959, Power realized that Xerography could be linked as a printing technique to materials preserved in microfilm form. He helped to develop a Xerox copier that worked directly from microfilm negatives, thereby achieving a printed form of his editions of one. This association with Xerox led in 1962 to the merger of University Microfilms into the Xerox Corporation. Power served on the Xerox board of directors until 1968. In 1970, he retired from the company because of its mandatory retirement age of 65.
Power had many interests beyond the business world. Concerned about the state of American college education, Power was twice elected to the board of regents of the University of Michigan (1955-1966). He was a member of the Association of College Governing Boards (president, 1970-71). In addition, he was a member of the governing boards of Carleton College, St. John's University, and the Interlochen Music School.
After his retirement, Power devoted most of his energies toward philanthropic concerns. In 1967, he established the Power Foundation and out of it came a series of initiatives that included the Power Exchange Scholarships, support for such causes as population control and the work of Planned Parenthood, and the development and construction of the Power Center for the Performing Arts at the University of Michigan. Eugene Power never really retired, always taking on new interests and responsibilities. He helped to found Eskimo Art, Inc., a non-profit corporation which first introduced the art of the Inuit of the Canadian northeast to the American market. He made numerous photographic safaris of wild game; he was chairman and principal motivator of the Ann Arbor Summer Festival; and he served on numerous boards of directors: Domino's Pizza, Daedalus Enterprises, and ERIM (Environmental Research Institute of Michigan).
Eugene Power died on December 7, 1993.
The Eugene Power collection consists of correspondence, agendas of meetings, memoranda, reports and printed material, diaries and photographs relating to his businesses, University of Michigan related activities and personal interests. The papers has been arranged into the following series: Personal/Biographical; University Microfilms Incorporated; Projected Books, Inc.; University of Michigan Board of Regents; Correspondence, 1949-1970; Organizational activities and personal interests; Photographs; Sound Recordings; and Microfilmed records.
As processing on this collection has not yet been completed, the researcher should note that this finding aid, with few exceptions, is not a listing of folders but rather a listing of the subject categories within the papers. All major subject categories (usually names of organizations or individuals) have been listed, but the amount of material within the category could be as much as several linear feet of files or as small as a single folder.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor (Mich.); Power, Eugene B., 1905-; University Microfilms.; University of Michigan. Board of Regents.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Power, Eugene B., 1905-
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Personal/Biographical
  - Biographical (includes clippings) (Box 1)
  - Speeches and Articles by EBP (Box 1)
  - Income tax records (Box 1)
  - Diaries, 1924-1927; 1936; 1949-1950; 1952-1955; 1959; 10 volumes (Box 2)
  - Photocopied typescripts of diaries (mainly travel), 1939-1974 (Box 2)
    (scattered dates, bulk 1960-1974)
- University Microfilms Incorporated
  - Chronological file, 1932-1970; 3 linear feet
    (includes articles, correspondence, photographs, brochures, memoranda, mailings, clippings, advertisements, etc)
    - 1932-1951 (Box 3)
    - 1952-1961 (Box 4)
    - 1962-1970 (Box 5)
  - Administrative records
    - Agreements (Box 6)
    - Copyright, 1962-1965 (Box 6)
    - Corporate papers and correspondence, 1952-1965 (Box 6)
      (include copies of earlier records)
    - Financial statements, 1938-1958; 1963-1964 (Box 6)
    - Merger files, 1962 (Box 7)
    - Personnel matters (charts, job descriptions, attitude survey, etc.) (Box 7)
    - Reports: Progress Reports, 1962-1964 (Box 7)
    - Reports: Progress Reports, 1965-1969 (Box 8)
    - Reports: Six months reports, 1963-1965 (Box 9)
    - Reports: Operations reports, 1963-1966 (Box 9)
    - Staff files (by date)
      - 1955-1966 (Box 9)
      - 1967-1969 (Box 10)
    - Staff files (by name)
      - Asleson, Robert, 1965-1969 (Box 10)
      - Lundy, James, 1964-1967 (Box 10)
      - Merlanti, Ernie, 1965-1969 (Box 10)
      - Peterson, Mabel (Box 10)
    - Staff miscellaneous
      - Employee Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 10)
      - Special reports, 1964 (Box 10)
      - Follow-up memoranda, 1964; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Xerox files (Box 11)
      (relations with parent company; largely arranged by office or department within the company)
    - UMI Limited, 1951-1967 (Box 12)
    - Inactive projects: include Duke of Bedford mss. microfilming 1952-1957 and Lord De L'Isle mss. microfilming, 1950-1964 (Box 13)
  - Topical files, 1946-1971
    - Alice's Adventures Under Ground (facsimile edition), 1963-1966; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - American Book Publishers Council, 1966-1967; 2 folders (Box 14)
    - American Library Association, 1968 (Box 14)
    - American Society for Information Science, 1966-1969 (Box 14)
    - Archives of the Indies, 1948-1954; 1958; 7 folders (Box 14)
    - Association of Research Libraries, 1963-1965 (Box 14)
    - Bahama Gazette, 1951-1954 (Box 14)
    - Carte (Rev. Thomas) manuscripts, 1946-1948 (Box 14)
    - Cataloging Short Title Catalog, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - China (Peoples Republic of), exchange of theses for Chinese publications, 1960-1961 (Box 14)
    - College Art, Metropolitan Museum, 1946-1947 (Box 14)
    - Commercial and Financial Chronicle, 1964-1965 (Box 14)
    - Committee to Rescue Italian Art (CRIA), 1966-1968; 3 folders (Box 14)
    - Congressional Record, 1953-1956 (Box 14)
    - Contributions from UMI to the University of Michigan, 1956-1966 (Box 14)
    - Copyright, 1965-1966 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence (miscellaneous), 1963-1970; 5 folders (Box 14)
    - Council on Library Resources, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - Deteriorating Book Preservation Project, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - Dissertation microfilming
      - General (Box 15)
      - Foreign, 1962-1966 (Box 15)
      - Indiana University, 1947-1954 (Box 15)
      - Thesis publication, 1953-1969 (Box 15)
    - Electro-Chemical Society symposia, 1966 (Box 15)
    - Evans, Luther, 1964-1965 (Box 15)
    - Executive Committee (meetings and reports), 1967-1969; 3 folders (Box 15)
    - Five-year plan, 1962-1965 (Box 15)
    - Genealogical Publishing Co., 1966-1967 (Box 15)
    - Graflex, 1962-1966 (Box 15)
    - Griscombe Products Corp., 1964 (Box 15)
    - Health, Education and Welfare (re Dissertation Abstracts), 1960-1961 (Box 15)
    - Historical Evaluation and Research Organization, 1963 (Box 15)
    - India project (Dr. Robert Frykenberg), 1965-1966 (Box 15)
    - International Micrographic Congress, 1963-1971; 0.5 linear feet (Box 15)
    - International Micrographic Congress, 1963-1971; 0.5 linear feet (Box 16)
    - Jefferson (Thomas) papers (correspondence with Julian Boyd), 1963 (Box 16)
    - Kampala, Uganda, 1963-1964 (Box 16)
    - Kids letters (possibility of book to be written by Bill Adler), 1965 (Box 16)
    - Lang (Peter Lang of Herman Lang & Cie AG Bern), 1963-1968; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Marketing Newsletter (also sales memos & reports), 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Marketing organization, 1964-1967 (Box 16)
    - Masters theses proposal, 1959 (Box 16)
    - Microfilm dealers, 1955 (Box 16)
    - Micro-Photo (package plan microfiche), 1963-1968 (Box 16)
    - Microcosm, 1955-1969 (Box 16)
    - Microscoop, 1965-1969 (Box 16)
    - Mullens (M.H. Mullen Co., Documentphoto), 1964-1965 (Box 16)
    - National Microfilm Association, 1959-1970; 0.5 linear feet (Box 17)
    - National Union Catalog (Box 17)
    - New building, 1964-1966; 0.5 linear feet (Box 17)
    - New Business Development Committee, 1966-1969; 4 folders (Box 18)
    - New York Times microfilm project, 1962-1963; 2 folders (Box 18)
    - News release material (Box 18)
    - North Carolina, University of, Press (Lambert Davis), 1948-1951 (Box 18)
    - Out-of-Print Books
      - Form letters, etc., 1958 (Box 18)
      - International, 1958-1960 (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous, 1958-1962 (Box 18)
      - Publishers cooperating (single title basis), 1958-1962 (Box 18)
      - Russell Press, 1958 (Box 18)
    - Profit Projections and Reports, 1965-1966 (Box 18)
    - Public Relations (Thurber, Gutenberg, Breck), 1964-1966 (Box 18)
    - Public Relations material, 1967-1968 (Box 18)
    - Publishers replies, 1963 (Box 18)
    - Rank Xerox Ltd., 1963-1966 (Box 18)
    - RCA-Electrofax, 1955-1956 (Box 18)
    - Readers & Printers, 1966-1969; 4 folders (Box 18)
    - Recruiting for UMI, 1962-1965 (Box 18)
    - Research and Microfilm Publications, Inc., 1963 (Box 19)
    - Retirement (letters received on occasion of his retirement from UMI), 1970 (Box 19)
    - Sales analysis charts, 1967 (Box 19)
    - Selective Dissemination of Information (SDI)--possible indexing of Dissertation Abstracts, 1964 (Box 19)
    - Sikkim (humanitarian and business interests), 1968-1969 (Box 19)
    - Trips abroad (arranged chronologically), 1942-1968; 13 folders (Box 19)
    - Trips (reports on UMI business trips), 1961-1962 (Box 19)
    - Union (labor), 1965 (Box 19)
    - United Nations Atomic Energy Commission, 1946 (Box 19)
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific & Cultural Organization-Microfilm laboratory, 1948 (Box 19)
    - Vanity Fair microfilm project, 1966 (Box 19)
    - Washington: Honorary dinner, 1958 (Box 19)
    - Wright, Louis B., 1966 (Box 19)
    - Xerox (files re UMI)
      - Contributions, 1967-1969 (Box 19)
      - Correspondence (miscellaneous), 1966-1971 (Box 19)
      - Fall Planning Conference, 1966 (Box 19)
      - London Planning Conference, 1963 (Box 19)
      - Market Research Report no. 6: "A Market Study of the Microfilm Industry", 1963-1964 (Box 19)
      - New York Xerox showroom, 1962-1965 (Box 19)
      - United Nations television show (letters of criticism and support), 1964 (Box 19)
  - Publications
    (articles, brochures, catalogs, etc.)
    - University Microfilms publications (Box 20)
    - Microfilm (general) publications (Box 20)
      (see also University Microfilms Chronological file, boxes 3-5)
- Projected Books Inc., 1944-1970
  - Minutes, 1944-1970 (Box 21)
  - Topical files: include some files of Microfilm Research Corporation, 1961-1965 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous (include financial records), 1944-1970 (Box 22)
  - Scrapbooks, 1946-1956; 3 volumes (Box 23)
  - Photographs (Box 23)
- University of Michigan Board of Regents, 1955-1966; 5 linear feet
  - Correspondence, 1955-March 1966
    - 1955-1960 (Box 24)
    - 1961-1964 (Box 25)
    - 1965-March 1966 (Box 26)
  - Yearly file of selective correspondence, reports, clippings, photos, etc., 1955-1966 (Box 26)
  - Topical file
    - A-D (Box 26)
    - E-Z (Box 27)
  - Alleged conflict of interest with UMI, 1966 (Box 27)
  - Regents' campaign files, 1955 (Box 28)
  - Regents' campaign files, 1963 (Box 28)
- Correspondence, 1949-1970
  - 1949-1970 (Box 29)
  - 1949-1970 (Box 30)
    (continued)
- Organizational activities and personal interests
  The great bulk of the collection documents Powers Organizational activities and personal interests. This series covers the period of approximately 1960 to 1993 and is arranged into several dated topical files subseries. The dating of the files is somewhat problematic as the files were not always retired to the library in a precisely chronological fashion. Thus while the bulk of the files may date in a given two or three year period, each accession will also include files from earlier years. Because of the size of the collection, no attempt has been made to interfile the several subseries into a single sequence. The researcher, interested in Power's involvement with any given organization, will be obliged to examine the container listing for each of the various subseries.
  - Topical files, mainly pre-1970
    - Airlines file, 1964-1970 (Box 31)
    - American Book Publishing Council, Reading Development Committee (Box 31)
    - American Council on Education (Box 31)
    - American Library in Pairs, 1970 (Box 31)
    - Ann Arbor Community Fund (Box 31)
    - Ann Arbor Rotary Club (Box 31)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Colleges and Universities (Box 31)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Colleges and Universities (Box 32)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Colleges and Universities (Box 33)
    - Broadcast Computer Service, 1970-1971 (Box 33)
    - Brown, Benjamin F., 1970 (Box 33)
    - Brown Brothers, Harriman and Co., 1969-1971 (Box 33)
    - Carleton College, 1966-1972 (Box 33)
    - Carleton College (Box 34)
    - Center for Applied Linguistics, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
    - Com-Share (Box 34)
    - Conlin Travel (Box 34)
    - Contributions, 1960-1970 (Box 34)
    - Daedalus Enterprises, 1969-1972 (Box 35)
    - Democratic Party (Box 35)
    - Dexter Lake Club, 1964-1970 (Box 35)
    - Dinner Group (Box 35)
    - Dramatic Arts Center (Box 35)
      see also oversize scrapbook, 1954-1957
    - Education (Box 36)
    - Enterprises (Box 36)
    - Explorers Club, 1970 (Box 36)
    - GCO, Inc., 1969-1972 (Box 36)
    - GCO, Inc. (Box 37)
    - Greater Michigan Foundation (Box 37)
    - Greenman Contract (Box 37)
    - Grolier Club, 1970-1971 (Box 37)
    - Infodata, 1970-1972 (Box 37)
    - Information Control Systems, 1970 (Box 37)
    - Institute of International Education (Box 37)
    - Insurance (Mundus and Mundus), 1966-1970 (Box 37)
    - Insurance (Fidelity), 1962 (Box 37)
    - Interlochen Arts Academy, 1968-1972 (Box 38)
    - International Congress of Orientalists (XXVII) (Box 38)
    - Investments (Box 38)
    - King, John L., 1962-1970 (Box 38)
    - KVOR station (Box 38)
    - Lathem, Edward C., 1970-1972 (Box 38)
    - Letters of Recommendation (Box 38)
    - Meier, Theo (Box 38)
    - Membership in Professional Societies, 1970 (Box 38)
    - Mexican Caper (Box 38)
    - Michigan Capital and Service (Box 38)
    - Michigan Capital and Service (Box 39)
    - Michigan Coordinating Council for Higher Education (re possible medical school at MSU, 1962) (Box 39)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1968-1970 (Box 39)
    - Observer Newspapers, 1968-1972 (Box 40)
    - Political (Box 40)
    - Porsches, 1966-1971 (Box 40)
    - Power, Philip (Box 40)
    - Programmed Instruction Project, 1964-1969 (Box 40)
    - Ranches (Box 40)
    - Recordings for Recovery, 1962-1970 (Box 40)
    - Regent Emeritus, 1967 (Box 40)
    - Regent Emeritus, 1968-1970 (Box 41)
    - Safari (Box 41)
    - St. John's University (MN), 1966-1971 (Box 41)
    - Staebler (Neil) Campaign Finance Committee, 1962-1964 (Box 41)
    - Sumiko Nitta, 1967-1970 (Box 42)
    - Travel/Tours, 1968-1970 (Box 42)
    - United Negro College Fund (Box 42)
    - United States-China Relations, 1967-1970 (Box 42)
    - University Theatre (Box 42)
    - White House (Box 42)
    - Wine Importers, Inc. (Box 42)
    - Winterthur, 1968-1970 (Box 42)
    - Woodrow Wilson Fellowships, 1966-1967 (Box 42)
    - Ypsilanti Greek Theatre (Box 42)
  - Topical files, mainly, 1971-1974
    - Arbor-A Inc., 1970-1974 (Box 43)
    - Association of Governing Boards of Colleges and Universities, 1973-1975 (Box 43)
    - Awards and honors, 1971-1974 (Box 43)
    - Business Committee for the Arts, 1972-1974 (Box 43)
    - Cancer Fund, 1974 (Box 43)
    - Committees and Boards, 1971-1974 (Box 43)
    - Common Cause, 1971-1974 (Box 43)
    - Contributions, 1971-1974 (Box 43)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 43)
    - Daedalus Enterprises, 1973 (Box 43)
    - Dexter Lake Club, 1971-1972 (Box 43)
    - Dinner Group, 1971-1974 (Box 43)
    - Education, 1971-1973 (Box 44)
    - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan (ERIM), 1972-1975 (Box 44)
    - Family Planning Medical Service, 1972-1974 (Box 45)
    - GCO, Inc., 1970-1975 (Box 45)
    - Interlochen Arts Academy, 1973-1975 (Box 46)
    - International Micrographic Congress, 1972-1974 (Box 46)
    - King, John L., 1971-1972 (Box 46)
    - Laser Systems, 1969-1972 (Box 46)
    - Lathem, Edward C., 1973 (Box 46)
    - March of America, 1973-1974 (Box 46)
    - Michigan Capital and Service (Box 46)
    - Michigan Council for the Arts, 1973-1975 (Box 46)
    - Microfilming-General, 1971-1974 (Box 46)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1968-1975 (Box 46)
    - National Microfilm Association, 1971-1974 (Box 47)
    - Observer Newspapers, 1971-1972 (Box 47)
    - Park Place Motor Inn (Box 47)
    - Park Place Motor Inn (Box 48)
    - Park Place Motor Inn (Box 49)
    - Planned Parenthood (Box 50)
    - Planned Parenthood (Box 51)
    - Planned Parenthood (Box 52)
    - Political (Box 53)
    - Power Foundation (Box 53)
    - Power Foundation (Box 54)
    - Power Foundation (Box 55)
    - Power Foundation (Box 56)
    - Power Center for the Performing Arts (Box 56)
    - Quakers (Box 56)
    - Real Estate Projects (Box 56)
    - Regent Emeritus, 1971-1974 (Box 57)
    - St. John's University, 1973 (Box 57)
    - St. Joseph's Mercy Hospital (Box 57)
    - Sikkim (Box 57)
    - Traverse City, Mich., 1971-1973 (Box 57)
    - United Negro College Fund, 1971-1974 (Box 57)
    - United States-China Relations, 1971-1973 (Box 57)
    - Vision, Inc., 1971-1972 (Box 57)
  - Topical files, mainly, 1975-1977
    - American Philosophical Society (Box 58)
    - Ann Arbor Art Association (Box 58)
    - Ann Arbor Symphony (Box 58)
    - Awards and honors (Box 58)
    - Barton Hills (Box 58)
    - Battle Abbey School (Box 58)
    - Biographical data (Box 58)
    - Borsook, Eve (Box 58)
    - Brown Brothers, Harriman and Co. (Box 58)
    - Business Committee for the Arts (Box 58)
    - Carter, John (Box 58)
    - Cherry Herring (Box 58)
    - China (Box 58)
    - Christmas (Box 58)
    - College Realty (Box 58)
    - Committees and Boards (Box 58)
    - Connable Office (includes earlier files) (Box 58)
    - Connable Office (Box 59)
    - Contributions (Box 59)
    - Coolidge, Jack (Box 60)
    - Correspondence (Box 60)
    - Daedalus Enterprises (Box 60)
    - Detroit Institute of Art (Box 60)
    - Dexter Lake Club (Box 60)
    - Dinner Group (Box 60)
    - Dunworkin Club (Box 60)
    - Education (Box 60)
    - Enterprises (Box 60)
    - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan (ERIM) (Box 60)
    - Environmental Research Institute of Michigan (ERIM) (Box 61)
    - Energy Conversion (Box 61)
    - GCO, Inc. (Box 62)
    - Greenebaum, Edgar (Box 62)
    - Grolier Club (Box 62)
    - Hastings, Battle of (Box 62)
    - Hoffman, Linda (Box 62)
    - Infodata (Box 62)
    - Insurance (Mundus and Mundus) (Box 62)
    - International Husky (Box 62)
    - International Micrographic Congress (Box 62)
    - Investments (Box 62)
    - KMS (Box 62)
    - KVOR (Colorado Springs) (includes earlier papers) (Box 63)
    - KVOR (Colorado Springs) (includes earlier papers) (Box 64)
    - KVOR (Colorado Springs) (Box 65)
    - Laporte, Adele (Box 65)
    - Letters of Recommendation (Box 65)
    - Library of Congress Fellows (Box 65)
    - Linowitz, Sol (Box 65)
    - Magdalene College (Box 65)
    - Marion Islands (Box 66)
    - Melcher, Daniel (Box 66)
    - Membership in Professional Societies (Box 66)
    - Metas, Christopher (Box 66)
    - Michigan Capital and Service (Box 66)
    - Michigan Council for the Arts (Box 66)
    - Michigan Council for the Arts (Box 67)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 67)
    - Michigan Savings and Loan (Box 67)
    - Microfilming (general) (Box 67)
    - Morrison, Mary Lou (Box 67)
    - Naset, Martha (Box 67)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 67)
    - National Microfilm Association (later National Micrographics Association) (Box 67)
    - Observer Newspapers (Box 67)
    - Park Place Motor Inn (Box 68)
    - Passigli, Stefano (Box 68)
    - Planned Parenthood (Box 68)
    - Plymouth Office Building (Box 68)
    - Political (Box 69)
    - Power Center for the Performing Arts (Box 69)
    - Power family members (Box 69)
    - Power Foundation (Box 69)
    - Power Foundation (Box 70)
    - Regent Emeritus (Box 70)
    - Regent Emeritus (Box 71)
    - Roberson, Mary Lou Morrison (Box 71)
    - Rotary Club (Box 71)
    - Safari (Box 71)
    - St. Joseph's Mercy Hospital (Box 71)
    - Saturday Review investment (Box 71)
    - Sharemet, John (Box 71)
    - Sikkim (Box 71)
    - Speeches (Box 71)
    - Suburban Communications (Box 71)
    - Tehensky Loan (Box 71)
    - Travel/Tours (Box 71)
    - Traverse City, Mich. (Box 71)
    - Trebilcock, Paul (Box 71)
    - Trout Unlimited (Box 71)
    - Twin Lakes Club (Box 72)
    - United Negro College Fund (Box 72)
    - United States-China Relations (Box 72)
    - University Microfilms (Box 72)
    - University Microfilms (Box 73)
    - Vision, Inc. (Box 73)
    - Works of Art (Box 73)